It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy!
Whoa, whoa, easy, boy, easy.
I-It's just Stewie in a kitty costume.
I'm a calico, and my name is Humphrey.
He got his face painted
at a birthday party.
It was the only thing
this little guy could do.
He was too light
for the caterpillar slide,
too short for the piñata,
and too scared to touch
the animals in the petting zoo.
- Half of them had erections.
The pony was magnificent.
- Oh, what do we have here?
- Hey, back off!
That's my goodie bag.
Ugh. An eraser.
Raisins in an unsealed sandwich bag.
Oh, a parachute guy.
Uhp, he's already tangled.
This day started off so great.
It was awash in cake and pony boners.
Now all I have is this dumb whistle.
Doesn't even work.
Ow! What the hell?!
Oh, it's a dog whistle.
I've always wondered
what that sounds like to you.
Dog whistle! Dog whistle!
Where are you, dog?!
- Give me that!
- Hey.
Oh, what, you want it? Here, take it.
Give it back.
- Give me it.
- No. It's mine now.
In fact, I'm gonna put it
where you can never reach it.
No!
Good luck, shrimp.
I can't believe the nerve of that dog.
Teaching me a lesson about size?
I'm not even that small.
Tiny Tom Cruise?
Oh, hey, little guy.
Forgot my sunglasses.
Hey, what's with
your gay character names lately?
Stacee Jaxx? Jack Reacher?
I mean, who are you playing next?
All right, try to make this sound gay:
next up, I play Headmaster Bates Mann.
- Anything else?
- Actually, yes.
After that, I'll be taking
the role of Major Dixon Butts,
then Senator Rod Clutcher.
I'm too small, am I, Brian?
Well, we'll just see
who's the bigger man.
"Brian, sorry I got testy.
Let's bury the hatchet.
"If you're free, I'd love to hear about
any new writing projects
you're working..."
Oh, at least wait for me to send it.
Hey, Stewie, I got your text.
What am I working on?
What am I not working on?
Well, first off, I got this
screenplay for Tom Cruise,
about the queen's private
secretary, Sir Gaylord Hummer.
Well, actually, he might do that.
But, Brian, I'm more interested
in short stories.
Well, hello there, little guy.
What the hell did you do to me, Stewie?
Well, Brian, you seemed
to enjoy belittling me,
so I decided to belittle you.
I've simply shrunken down
your molecular structure.
It was easy, really.
Like taking candy,
or a whistle, from a baby.
You dick. Undo this.
This is perfect.
I think my excitement is best expressed
by Jean-Claude Van Damme in this scene.
All right, you've made
your point. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I couldn't hear that,
it's too high-pitched.
- You're what?
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
- For calling you a shrimp.
- And?
- What do you mean "and"?
Come on, you know what I want.
And... all four chairs
would totally turn for you on The Voice.
Anything else?
And the way you salute
and point is very casual
and free of affectation.
Hey, thanks, Bri.
I'll go switch you back.
Stewie!
You know, I'm really flattered you think
all four Voice chairs would turn around.
My dream order would be Adam, Blake,
Alicia Keys, and then Kelly Clarkson,
whose chair I imagine would turn last,
'cause she's, uh... she's a bigger gal.
Help!
Oh, crap.
Don't worry, Brian, I'll save you!
But I'm a millennial,
so first I have to watch
a YouTube instructional video
on how to do it.
What's going on, guys?
I'm Corey, and today I'm gonna teach you
how to get your friend
out of a rat hole.
Now, before we get started,
don't forget to subscribe
to my channel, Corey's World.
And, guys, I'll get to
as many comments as I can,
but I can't get to all of them.
And don't forget to check out
my other videos,
like "How to Play Guitar."
Uh, Brian, this might be a while.
What's going on, guys? I'm Corey.
Brian! Hang in there, buddy.
Hurry up! Get this rat away from me!
I'll shrink myself down
and come get you.
But in the meantime, they say
if you put your finger in
a rat's butt, that disables it.
It didn't work. Now he's just angry.
Try wetting your finger first.
Just get in here!
Hey, come on, guy.
Hey, you don't want to do this.
I'll have what she's having.
Please tell me that's not the finger
you stuck in a rat's butt.
No. It... I don't-I don't
remember which one it was.
Yeah, that was the finger.
All right, let's get back
to the machine.
Look at all this shag carpet.
This is like our Vietnam movie.
I miss Jenny.
- What is that?
- That's Forrest. Forrest Gump.
- Yeah, I-I don't think so.
- Shh.
What is that?
It ain't a box of chocolates.
Vacuum cleaner!
I hate my life and nobody
can hear me say it right now!
Oh, my God, this is disgusting!
I just hope she's done vacuuming.
Okay, everyone,
dump your toenails in the hall,
I'm vacuuming.
Oh, God.
That was close.
Oh, my God, we're in the trash outside!
We've got to get down from here.
Quick, pass me that baggie.
How am I supposed to get down?
That was the only baggie.
Use either the tampon strings
or the discarded dental floss
and rappel down.
Which one did you go with?
Neither. I was hoping to kill myself.
Two days of mail at once, nobody knows.
Don't go over two. Don't get greedy.
Uhp, got a bat in the cave.
All right, I figure if we can just...
What's going on? An eclipse?
- Ah! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- Holy crap! What is that?!
- Gross! Oh!
- What is on us? Oh!
Ah! Snot rocket!
Oh, my God, it's so disgusting!
Get it off! Get it off!
- Are you guys eating that?
- Uh, what?
Are you eating this pile of boogers?
- Uh, no.
- Can I eat it?
Yeah, please. We're stuck.
Dude, dude, you got to get down
here, by the big trash can.
Dude, dude, dude, just get here.
- Brian, we've got to get up to my room.
- Yeah, but how?
We'll just climb the lattice
on the front of the house.
- When did we get that?
- Well, every '80s movie had one,
so the fat man thought
we should have one, too.
Wow. Okay, great.
You know, it's funny,
you said "every '80s movie,"
but I can't think of a single one.
- Ferris Bueller's Day Off?
- I don't think so.
But the lattice thing
sounded right when you said it.
I-I feel like '80s movies
were wall-to-wall lattices.
- Sixteen Candles?
- Hmm... no, no.
I mean, she was being ignored
most of the movie.
Who'd be climbing into her window?
Ah, good point. Risky Business?
No. Hookers don't climb.
Oh, I know, Home Alone.
Home Alone must've had a lattice.
Maybe, but that was 1990.
Eh, it feels like an '80s movie.
You know, it was probably
greenlit in the '80s,
when lattices were still a thing.
Oh, wow, here we are.
All right, Brian, at this size,
this is a two-man job.
While I adjust the settings,
you go over there
and hit the tiny button to fire it up.
Wait a minute.
This doesn't feel right.
What button did you hit?
That one. The tiny button.
Wait, did you hit the tiny button
or the button that says "tiny"?
I hit the button that says "tiny."
- You said, "Hit the tiny button."
- Exactly!
I didn't say, "Hit the big
button that says 'tiny, '"
I said, "hit the tiny button."
The one you pressed
is going to shrink us down
to microscopic size!
Well, why would you make
the tiny button big?
I had to make it big enough
to write "tiny" on it!
Well, what the hell do we do now?!
I don't...
I-I'm still thinking
about that lattice thing.
I want to say Parenthood?
Parenthood. Yes.
I feel like Parenthood is right.
It's beautiful.
Ah, I just wish my hot
girlfriend were here to see it.
Oh, yeah? Yeah, you have a girlfriend?
- What's her name?
- Girly... Friendston.
"Girly Friendston"? Nice try, Stewie.
Why won't he answer my texts?
Girly, your piano teacher's here.
- Oh, Mom, do I have to?
- Girly Friendston,
you stop mooning over
that boyfriend of yours
and get down here this instant.
Hi. I'm the exterminator.
An ex-Terminator?
So you used to be a Terminator?
- No. I kill rats and bugs.
- And Sarah Connor.
- No, Peter. We have a rat.
- My stuff's in my truck.
I'll be back.
See that, Lois?
There's more Terminators around
than you think there are.
I hope he can terminate
some of the bad attitudes
on our kids, huh?
Yeah.
What's that sound?
Oh, my God! Look!
Holy crap, what the hell
were those things?!
Dust mites.
One of the most dominant species
of the micro world.
Why did they just attack like that?
Because they're jerks.
Aah! Who the hell are you?
Sorry. Didn't mean to scare you,
little buddies.
My name's Vernon. I'm a water bear.
A water bear? What's a water bear?
They're predominantly
water-dwelling, eight-legged
segmented micro animals.
They're also known as
a moss piglet or a tardigrade.
You can call me tardy,
but I'm always on time.
Ha-ha. Yeah.
Well, here she is. Home sweet home.
Everybody, we've got guests!
You'll see that we have quite
the diverse cast of characters.
I'm the country water bear.
"Yee-haw" is what I say.
Flagellum? I don't even know them.
I'm the black one.
And I'm Patrick Stewart as a water bear.
I can't believe there's
this whole universe
hidden here in your rug...
where everyone speaks English.
Okay, Brian, take the ride.
Here, have a sip of water.
What the...? Hey, cut it out!
You have water? Water is life.
Yeah, we need water bad.
And I'm the gay one, but I'm
not, like, doing the gay voice.
Listen, Stewie and I come from a place
where water flows like... well, water.
That's right.
And we need to get back there.
And if you guys help us,
we'll make sure you never
want for water again.
What do you say?
All right!
Patrick Stewart!
- Well, what'd you find?
- I'll be honest.
I think this is a conversation
best had over dinner.
Oh. Okay.
So what's going on with the house?
I don't like talking business
at the table.
- Let's just enjoy our wine.
- You're right. I'm sorry.
Your wife's asleep.
Sometimes she fakes it
so I can't hump her,
but this seems legit.
So, uh, shouldn't we talk about
what you found at our house?
I don't know. It's so late.
I have a crazy idea.
Should we talk about it over a nightcap?
Uh, sure, I guess.
I'm a little chilly.
Oh, well, I-I guess I don't need this.
Sir? Sir, I asked you what
you found out about the house.
What? Oh. You're gonna
have to tent the house.
All right. Thanks for your work.
You're very professional.
Yeah, that's me. Professional.
Always professional.
And alone.
What the hell is this giant wall?
We're here, Brian. That's your laptop.
If we get inside, I can remotely
hack into the shrink ray.
Oh, my God! It's the dust mites!
Oh, no! Water Bear Consuela,
can you stop them?
No, no. I only clean Wednesday.
- Can't you just clean today?
- No, no. Wednesday.
Here's the micro board.
I just need to reroute the circuits.
All right. The laptop is now
linked to the shrink ray.
The only problem is that
I can't activate it from here.
We still somehow have to press
the return button on the keyboard.
But at this size, there's no way
I can do it alone.
Wait. I've got an idea.
Well, you better act quickly.
Guys! Follow me up this way!
Why is there a tiny lattice
inside this computer?
I guess Steve Jobs was
really into '80s movies.
Brian, wait for my signal.
Hold.
- Now!
- You-you never told me what to do.
- Jump!
- Why?
- Trust me.
- Aah!
My God! It worked!
Stewie, you're a genius!
Oh, no.
Run!
Okay. All the gas bombs are set up.
Time to blow all those vermin
to kingdom come.
Can I press the button?
Hmm, perhaps that's a question
best pondered over dinner?
You-you can just press it. Go ahead.
Aah! Poison gas!
They must've gotten
an exterminator for the rat!
Tiny Tom Cruise?
Thank you, Tiny Tom Cruise.
How can we ever repay you?
Well, you could make a sizable donation
to the Church of Spaceship Beep Boop.
You mean the Church of...
Yeah, kidnapping, torture,
extortion, that's the one.
And we won't get in trouble
because we didn't use the actual name.
What did he just say?
We are about love and
spaceships and beep boop!
Get my lawyer on the phone!
- You have children in there?!
- Oh, yeah, three.
Should-should we have mentioned that?
Meg, Chris, come to the light.
Meg, no. Don't do it.
Don't go to Prince!
Come to the purple light, Meg.
Come taste infinity.
Don't listen to him, Meg.
But he's so talented
and he's got so many drugs.
Alan Thicke is here, too.
Hey, guys. Come on in. It's a hoot.
I'm coming, Alan Thicke.
No!
Google my CrystaLight
aerobics competition.
It's ridiculous.
I hope Vernon and the gang survived.
That gas was pretty powerful.
Well, let's take a look.
They're okay.
Let's deliver on our promise.
A little water for our little friends.
- Oh, hell no!
- Set country music!
Oh, my gay God.
Ah, they're dead. Now I'm sad.
Cheer me up, Jean-Claude Van Damme.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.tv